

# Teixeira

React Developer

Portfolio: dantxal.com

github.com/dantxal

dantxal@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/daniel-txal

## About me

Hello, I am Daniel Teixeira, 26-years old, Full Stack developer, I'm very tech-savvy and a React enthusiast.

I started studying React in the first-half of 2019, and have been working and studying it together with NodeJS and React Native.

I like to keep myself updated with new technologies and metodologies in this spectrum.

am proficient in spoken and written English.

## Professional Experience

Full Stack Developer

Full Time

Snapboard Inc. PRemote

Oct, 2019 - Aug, 2020

Product design, implementing integrations, creating components, e2e testing. Typescript, React, NodeJS, Cypress.io, Passport

### React Developer

Freelance

Freelancing

Remote

Jun, 2019 - Oct, 2019

Comissioned apps for local businesses. React, Electron

## Education

#### React Tech Stack - Bootcamp

🗀 Jul, 2017 - Jul, 2021 Rocketseat

Imersive course on the React, Node and React Native ecosystem. Many practical exercises, developed entire apps with databases, back-end, front-end and mobile.

The course also included:

- DevOps with docker, mongodb, postgres;
- Advanced styling using styled-components library;
- State management with Redux and Redux-Saga;
- Tests with Jest.

## **Javascript and React Courses**

Apr, 2019 - May, 2019

codewithmosh.com

Introductory course to Javascript ES6, and React. During the course I developed an entire Video Rental app with a fake API.

#### **English Course**

**Jan, 2007 - Dec, 2011** 



A 5-years long course with both written and oral tests every semester. The course aims at teaching students everything they might need if they ever decide to study/work in a English-speaking country.